pscu.org 2008-06-19

# About PSCU - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY NOTICE DISCLOSURE 

Public Service Credit Union (PSCU) is owned by its members and governed by a board of directors that you elect. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a top priority of this credit union. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your personal financial information. If you have any questions, please contact a member service representative at (303) 691-2345 or (800) 437-7328. 

We are committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs, which necessitates that we share information about you to complete your transactions and to provide you with certain financial opportunities. In order to do so, we have entered into agreements with other companies that provide either services for us or additional financial products for you to consider. 

To protect our members' privacy, we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell the information we provide to other third parties. 

Information We Collect And Disclose About You   
We collect the following nonpublic personal information about you from a variety of sources and may disclose all the information we collect, as described below, as permitted by law and in accordance with our privacy policy. 

  * From membership and loan applications and other forms, we obtain information such as name, address, social security number and income. 
  * From your transactions with our affiliates, we obtain information such as your account balances, payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage. 
  * From consumer reporting agencies, we obtain information such as your creditworthiness and credit history. 
  * From verifications of information you provide on applications and other forms, we obtain information from current or past employers, other financial institutions and other sources listed on the application. 

In order that we may provide you competitive products and services, we may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf and to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, to follow your instructions you authorize, to conduct the operations of the credit union, or to protect the security of our financial records. 

If you terminate your membership with Public Service Credit Union, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as permitted or required by law. 

How We Protect Your Information   
We restrict access to nonpublic information about you to those employees who have a specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and leading industry practices to safeguard your nonpublic personal information. 

Notice Under Fair Credit Reporting Act   
We are permitted by law to share any information about transactions or experiences with you. However, information taken from credit reports will not be exchanged or shared with anyone. 

What Members Can Do To Help Protect Their Privacy   
While we are committed to protecting the privacy of our members, there are certain things that you can do to protect the privacy of your personal information. Such as: 

  * Protect your account numbers, plastic card numbers; personal identification numbers (PINs) or passwords. 
  * Protect the transmission of your information sent through e-mail, messages should be sent through our secure server through our personal branch on-line banking service. 
  * All passwords or PIN information should be kept confidential and in a separate location away from or on your computer, not in your wallet, or on any card. 
  * Use caution when disclosing account numbers, social security numbers, or other information to other persons. Our staff will ask for this information for identification purposes. 

Rev. 11/06
